<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pageContent>
    <id><![CDATA[OTS_SA_R5_D070_A020]]></id>
	<title><![CDATA[]]></title>
    <descriptionText><![CDATA[<Introtext style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:16pt; font-weight:bold; color:#cc0033; margin:10px; padding:0 0 0 5px; background:#e8e8e8; border-bottom:1px solid #333; display:block;">Understanding the Context</Introtext><welcomeText style=" font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; line-height:18pt; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal; color:#333; display:block; margin:0 10px 10px">This is an Execute Next Steps question, but it doesn’t build on the previous conversation. It might advance the conversation to this specific topic, but it’s closed-ended, and it doesn’t engage Dr. Chu in partnering to create value. <BR> <BR>
        
        The best question is, “You’ve mentioned consulting more with Pharmacy, and I understand your desire to be familiar with the safety profile of what you prescribe.  When you consider trying a product you have never used before, such as Samsca, what factors are important to you?” <BR> <BR>
        This Execute Next Steps question moves you toward taking action and helps you to better understand how to position yourself as an advisor to decision makers. <BR> <BR>
        <B> It will help you to know the answer to this question to continue.  Here is how Dr. Chu would have answered:</B>  <BR> <BR>
        
        “I’ll begin by saying that I would very rarely be one of the first people in a hospital to try a product.  As you know, I’m cautious and safety-focused, so I wouldn’t begin a new product unless Pharmacy supported it or I had peers with experience prescribing it.  In my position as a hospitalist, I see such a wide variety of patients that I can’t be fully up to speed on the specialized therapies they might need.  That’s why the specialist consults are important. <BR> <BR>
        
        However, if the product was already adopted and supported by the hospital and Pharmacy, then I must be comfortable with the drug’s safety and efficacy profile, and it must be available at a reasonable cost.”</welcomeText>]]></descriptionText>
    <character><![CDATA[Mac_skeptical]]></character>
    <continueBtn><![CDATA[]]></continueBtn>	
	<branchTo><![CDATA[OTS_SA_R5_D080]]></branchTo>
</pageContent>








