<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pageContent>
    <id><![CDATA[OC_SA_R1_INTRO_3]]></id>
	<title><![CDATA[Introduction3]]></title>
    <descriptionText><![CDATA[<Introtext style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:16pt; font-weight:bold; color:#cc0033; margin:10px; padding:0 0 0 5px; background:#e8e8e8; border-bottom:1px solid #333; display:block;">Your Customer</Introtext><welcomeText style=" font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; line-height:18pt; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal; color:#333; display:block; margin:0 10px 10px">Sunnydale Psychiatry is a busy psychiatric practice located in the heart of a metropolitan district.  Three psychiatrists and one APRN practice at the facility.  The lead psychiatrist is Dr. Bernard Hayes, but your primary contact for the last year has been with Dr. Will Bennett, a younger doctor who has been more receptive to prescribing your product.<br><br><span style="color:#3366cc; font-size:12pt; font-weight:bold">Basic information about doctors and staff at Sunnydale Psychiatry:</span><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Dr. Bernard Hayes started the practice 20 years ago</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Other clinical staff include Dr. Will Bennett, Dr. Teresa Roberts, and Angela, APRN</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">With the exception of Dr. Hayes, all clinical staff rotate to other facilities, including local <span style="margin:0 0 0 15px;">hospitals</span> and community mental health centers</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Dr. Hayes wants to continue growing the practice, and at least somewhat reduce the time the <span style="margin:0 0 0 15px;">other</span> clinical staff spends at different facilities.<br><br><span style="color:#3366cc; font-size:12pt; font-weight:bold">General practice trends related to Sunnydale Psychiatry:</span></li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Sunnydale Psychiatry has one of the highest volumes of patients with depression in the city</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Currently, your product is prescribed rarely by the physicians, typically as a last resort
	</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">In general, the office prefers to "stick to what has worked in the past"</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">As the office gets busier, it is beginning to restrict access to the staff</li><BR>You’ve built a solid relationship with Dr. Bennett over the past year, and you have seen an increase in his use of your product in the office.  However, you now have your sights set on increasing the prescribing of all the doctors in the office and on establishing your product as the atypical of choice. After working with Annie, you have decided that this should be your global A to B shift with this practice. You know that Dr. Hayes wants the practice to grow.  You believe you’ve also positioned yourself as a valued resource: the office appreciates your deep product knowledge and understanding of their practice, as well as the promotional program opportunities you provide.<BR><BR>You have a strong understanding of Sunnydale Psychiatry.  It’s clear that with the right approach, they could become one of your largest accounts.</welcomeText><br><lasttext style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:11pt; color:#000; background-color:#c0c0c0; margin:10px; padding:2px 0 2px 5px; display:block;"><i>Please click the <b>Continue</b> button begin the simulation.<i></lasttext]]></descriptionText>
    <continueBtn><![CDATA[]]></continueBtn>
	<branchTo><![CDATA[]]></branchTo>
</pageContent>