<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pageContent>
  <id><![CDATA[OTS_SA_R5_INTRO_2]]></id>
  <title><![CDATA[Introduction 2]]></title>
  <descriptionText><![CDATA[<font face="helvetica" size="3"><Introtext style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:16pt; font-weight:bold; color:#cc0033; margin:10px; padding:0 0 0 5px; background:#e8e8e8; border-bottom:1px solid #333; display:block;">You and Your Customer</Introtext><welcomeText style=" font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; line-height:18pt; text-align:justify; font-weight:normal; color:#333; display:block; margin:0 10px 10px">Sunnydale Psychiatry is a busy psychiatric practice located in the heart of a metropolitan district.  Three psychiatrists and one APRN practice at the facility.  The lead psychiatrist is Dr. Bernard Hayes, though your closer relationship is with Dr. Will Bennett.<BR><BR>Basic information about Sunnydale Psychiatry:<BR><BR><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Dr. Bernard Hayes started the practice 20 years ago</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Other clinical staff include Dr. Will Bennett, Dr. Teresa Roberts, and Angela Martinez, APRN</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">With the exception of Dr. Hayes, all clinical staff rotate to other facilities, including local <span style="margin:0 0 0 16px;">hospitals</span> and community mental health centers</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Dr. Hayes wants to continue growing the practice, and at least somewhat reduce the time the <span style="margin:0 0 0 16px;">other</span> clinical staff spend at different facilities</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">Sunnydale Psychiatry has one of the highest volumes of patients with depression in the city</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">In general, the office prefers to "stick to what has worked in the past"</li><li style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:12pt; color:#333; list-style-type:disc;">As the office gets busier, it is beginning to restrict access to the staff</li><BR>You’ve built a solid relationship with the prescribers in the office over the past year, and you have seen an increase in the use of your product.  As you continue to interact with all of the prescribers and office staff at Sunnydale Psychiartry, you want to be sure that you are aware of, and proactively managing, the concerns of all the staff.  Recently, you’ve had some conversations with Rachel Dawson, the office manager at Sunnydale Psychiatry.  Through her, you’ve learned that as the practice continues to grow, the office staff are focusing more and more on increasing efficiency.  From previous conversations with Dr. Bennett and Dr. Hayes, you know that patient satisfaction is key to the practice’s strategy for growth.<BR><BR>You’ve arranged a meeting with Rachel to discuss how you can support Sunnydale Psychiatry in their goals of increasing efficiency and patient satisfaction.  To confirm that meeting, you sent Rachel an email.</welcomeText><br><br><lasttext style="font-family:Helvetica; font-size:11pt; color:#000; background-color:#c0c0c0; margin:10px; padding:2px 0 2px 5px; display:block;"><i>Please press or swipe the <b>CONTINUE</b> button to move to the next screen.</i></lasttext>]]></descriptionText>
  <continueBtn><![CDATA[]]></continueBtn>
  <branchTo><![CDATA[]]></branchTo>
</pageContent>
